<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jestarling</title>
    <link>https://jestarling.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jestarling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 12:15:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jestarling.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jennifer.</title>
      <link>https://jestarling.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 12:15:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jestarling.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD candidate at The University of Texas at Austin in the Department of Statistics and Data Sciences, working with professors James Scott, Jared Murray, Carlos Carvalho, and Abigail Aiken.
My research interests are in developing flexible Bayesian models for structured data, tree-based methods, and causal inference, with applications to public health and medicine. My recent work has focused on women&amp;rsquo;s healthcare, obstetrics, and family planning. Prior to joining UT, I completed my MS in Statistics at Texas A&amp;amp;M University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact me.</title>
      <link>https://jestarling.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 12:15:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jestarling.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can email me at jestarling [at] utexas [dot] edu.
Follow me on Twitter at @starlingje.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research.</title>
      <link>https://jestarling.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 12:15:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jestarling.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>My complete CV is available here. Papers are available on my Google Scholar page.   Deshpande, SK and Bai, R and Balocchi, C and Starling, JE. VC-BART: Bayesian trees for varying coefficients. In preparation, 2020.
  Starling, JE, Aiken, CE, and Murray, JS, and Nakimuli, A and Scott, JG. Monotone function estimation in the presence of extreme data coarsening: Analysis of pre-eclampsia and birth weight in urban Uganda. Under review, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software.</title>
      <link>https://jestarling.github.io/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 12:15:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jestarling.github.io/software/</guid>
      <description>tsBART BART with Targeted Smoothing. Companion R package to this paper. Includes Projective Smooth BART functionality from this paper. Companion Shiny app is available here.
tsBCF Targeted Smooth Bayesian Causal Forests. Companion R package to this paper. Companion Shiny app is available here.
VC-BART Bayesian trees for varying coefficients. Companion R package to (coming soon).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>